<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<jennyKSite>
<?processing instructions?>
	<section title="design" id="1" navY="146">
		<item title="Jivaka" id="1" p="200">
			<copy><![CDATA[Jivaka is a developer of green, modern, luxury homes that focuses not only on protecting natural resources, but also on the individuals living in the homes by using building materials that are protective of their health. The logo was designed to convey a feeling of serenity and fluidity, with an eye towards the green and humanistic aspects of the living spaces. <br/><br/>Shown here is the business card and signage used at site properties, followed by the website landing page.]]></copy>
			<image source="JKimages/des_Jivaka_1_sect_1.jpg" id="1"></image>
			<image source="JKimages/des_Jivaka_2_sect_1.jpg" id="2"></image>
		</item>
		<item title="Pooh" id="2" p="180">
			<copy><![CDATA[The objective of the Winnie the Pooh for Grown-ups Too style guide was twofold: to provide Disney licensees with the design elements for use in their merchandising and to incorporate those elements into the guide itself. Shown here is the typographic style I developed, replacing type characters with icons, which was used throughout the 450-page style guide. A “storybook” look for the tab pages was also created, evolving into the designs featured on the following pages.]]></copy>
			<image source="JKimages/des_Pooh_1_sect_2.jpg" id="1"></image>
			<image source="JKimages/des_Pooh_2_sect_2.jpg" id="2"></image>
			<image source="JKimages/des_Pooh_3_sect_2.jpg" id="3"></image>
		</item>
		<item title="American Funds" id="3" p="180">
			<copy><![CDATA[This is an 8-page brochure that was used to launch a new sales initiative to expand the reach of American Funds — one of the top 3 mutual fund firms in the U.S. — to a more sophisticated sector of advisors. The photography style used was effective in distinguishing this marketing piece from the general retail pieces, and the layout helped to visually reinforce the message of consistency. This piece was well received, appealing to both brokers and their clients.]]></copy>
			<image source="JKimages/des_American_Funds_1_sect_3.jpg"></image>
		</item>
		<item title="American Funds" id="4" p="138">
			<copy><![CDATA[Aimed at the financial adviser community, these postcards were designed as a series of short, succinct, visually attractive mailings designed to announce American Funds’ expansion of their share class offerings. The mailing led with the “choice” card, followed by subsequent mailings that focused on individual share class-specific information.]]></copy>
			<image source="JKimages/des_Share_1_sect_4.jpg"></image>
		</item>
		<item title="Saraswati" id="5" p="263">
			<copy><![CDATA[In 2008 I decided to develop a business that combined my love for design with my love for yoga and its country of origin. It’s a work in progress that requires being open to the unknown and trusting my instincts, even when it’s not clear where the path may lead. Very transformational, very fun... <br/><br/>The logo is intended to appeal to anyone, not just those familiar with the world of yoga. Saraswati is the goddess of knowledge and creativity. The circular design represents the second chakra — the seat of creativity — and the heart is where our greatest wisdom resides. <br/><br/>Shown here is the business card, product insert and hangtag.]]></copy>
			<image source="JKimages/des_Sara_Soul_1_sect_5.jpg"></image>
		</item>
		<item title="Capital Group" id="6" p="162">
			<copy><![CDATA[Capital Group Companies wanted to bring together its in-house reporters from around the country for a two-day seminar to help them enhance their news-gathering and communication skills. Their goals were serious, the agenda full, but they also wanted to have fun. The less conservative alternative to the usual plain white binders: bold graphics and colorful tab pages that clearly distinguished one topic from another.]]></copy>
			<image source="JKimages/des_Com_Changes_1_sect_6.jpg"></image>
		</item>
		<item title="Capital Group" id="7" p="140">
			<copy><![CDATA[Capital Bank and Trust, a subsidiary of Capital Group Companies, needed to create a branded identity of its own yet still be able to leverage the solid name recognition of its parent company. The solution: a distinctive two-color letterhead, envelopes and business cards that featured conservative, all-caps type juxtaposed against a more contemporary script.]]></copy>
			<image source="JKimages/des_CBT_1_sect_7.jpg"></image>
		</item>
		<item title="Financial Advisors" id="8" p="202">
			<copy><![CDATA[Financial advisors needed a simple way to present retirement plan participants with side-by-side options when it came to deciding what to do with their 401(k) funds when leaving their jobs. This brochure, designed with an introductory gatefold that opened out to a four-panel spread, allowed the financial advisor to visually and sequentially review the options with plan participants. This approach allowed for white space and graphics to help the reader navigate each option with greater ease, with or without the guidance of an advisor.]]></copy>
			<image source="JKimages/des_Rollover_1_sect_8.jpg" id="1"></image>
			<image source="JKimages/des_Rollover_1_sect_8_b.jpg" id="2"></image>
		</item>
		<item title="Numbers" id="9" p="140">
			<copy><![CDATA[Offering a colorful graphic alternative to the photographic imagery typically preferred by this client, this sales brochure cover represented an evolution in branding possibilities. Moving forward, the company chose to develop collateral materials for their brokers that embodied less-traditional, more visually striking graphic treatments.]]></copy>
			<image source="JKimages/des_Numbers_1_sect_9.jpg"></image>
		</item>
		<item title="Financial Education" id="10" p="222">
			<copy><![CDATA[These tri-fold brochures are from a design system I developed for a series of short educational pieces provided to financial advisors nationwide. They are used to accompany presentations and/or enclosed in payroll envelopes as standalone pieces. The concepts being communicated were challenging — saving and investing — and had to be presented in a way that made the subject seem simple and personally compelling. The developed system maintained a unified look overall, but allowed layout flexibility on the insides of the brochures, to avoid a cookie cutter approach as the number of brochure topics expanded.]]></copy>
			<image source="JKimages/des_IFL_1_sect_10.jpg"></image>
		</item>
	</section>
	<section title="illustration" id="2" navY="165">
		<item title="" id="1">
			<copy><![CDATA[Illustrations are displayed exclusively for viewing by clients and prospective clients. All copyrights belong to Jenny Kay unless otherwise indicated.]]></copy>
			<image source="JKimages/ill_image01.jpg"></image>
		</item>
		<item title="" id="2">
			<copy><![CDATA[]]></copy>
			<image source="JKimages/ill_image02.jpg"></image>
		</item>
		<item title="" id="3">
			<copy><![CDATA[]]></copy>
			<image source="JKimages/ill_image03.jpg"></image>
		</item>
		<item title="" id="4">
			<copy><![CDATA[]]></copy>
			<image source="JKimages/ill_image04.jpg"></image>
		</item>
		<item title="" id="5">
			<copy><![CDATA[]]></copy>
			<image source="JKimages/ill_image05.jpg"></image>
		</item>
		<item title="" id="6">
			<copy><![CDATA[]]></copy>
			<image source="JKimages/ill_image06.jpg"></image>
		</item>
		<item title="" id="7">
			<copy><![CDATA[]]></copy>
			<image source="JKimages/ill_image07.jpg"></image>
		</item>
		<item title="" id="8">
			<copy><![CDATA[]]></copy>
			<image source="JKimages/ill_image08.jpg"></image>
		</item>
		<item title="" id="9">
			<copy><![CDATA[Illustrations are displayed exclusively for viewing by clients and prospective clients. Illustration copyright belongs to ABC/Disney.]]></copy>
			<image source="JKimages/ill_image09.jpg"></image>
		</item>
		<item title="" id="10">
			<copy><![CDATA[Illustrations are displayed exclusively for viewing by clients and prospective clients. Illustration copyright belongs to ABC/Disney.]]></copy>
			<image source="JKimages/ill_image10.jpg"></image>
		</item>
		<item title="" id="11">
			<copy><![CDATA[]]></copy>
			<image source="JKimages/ill_image11.jpg"></image>
		</item>
		<item title="" id="12">
			<copy><![CDATA[]]></copy>
			<image source="JKimages/ill_image12.jpg"></image>
		</item>
	</section>
	<section title="photography" id="3" navY="188">
		<item title="" id="1">
			<copy><![CDATA[These photos are a sampling of images captured as I've traveled through India over the past few years. Some of the more well-known cities visited are Agra, Bangalore, Delhi, Goa, Hampi, Jaipur, Kanyakumari, Karauli, Kerala, Kumarakom, Madurai, Mumbai, Ranthambore and Varanasi.<br/><br/>May these simple, graphic images stir your curiosity and take you into the stillness of the moment, out of the world you know to a place thousands of miles away rich with endless color and contrast.<br/><br/>Custom, archival quality prints, meaning they should last at least 60 years, are available for purchase. Please contact me for further information. All image copyrights belong exclusively to SaraswatiSoul.]]></copy>
			<image source="JKimages/photo/jkd_goddess_p1.jpg"></image>
		</item>
		<item title="" id="2">
			<copy><![CDATA[]]></copy>
			<image source="JKimages/photo/jkd_bathsign_p2.jpg"></image>
		</item>
		<item title="" id="3">
			<copy><![CDATA[]]></copy>
			<image source="JKimages/photo/jkd_sadu_p3.jpg"></image>
		</item>
		<item title="" id="4">
			<copy><![CDATA[]]></copy>
			<image source="JKimages/photo/jkd_hampilove_p4.jpg"></image>
		</item>
		<item title="" id="5">
			<copy><![CDATA[]]></copy>
			<image source="JKimages/photo/jkd_dontspit_p5.jpg"></image>
		</item>
		<item title="" id="6">
			<copy><![CDATA[]]></copy>
			<image source="JKimages/photo/jkd_whitehot_p6.jpg"></image>
		</item>
		<item title="" id="7">
			<copy><![CDATA[]]></copy>
			<image source="JKimages/photo/jkd_jaipur_p7.jpg"></image>
		</item>
		<item title="" id="8">
			<copy><![CDATA[]]></copy>
			<image source="JKimages/photo/jkd_pepsi_p8.jpg"></image>
		</item>
		<item title="" id="9">
			<copy><![CDATA[]]></copy>
			<image source="JKimages/photo/jkd_likearock_p9.jpg"></image>
		</item>
		<item title="" id="10">
			<copy><![CDATA[]]></copy>
			<image source="JKimages/photo/jkd_gayatri_p10.jpg"></image>
		</item>
		<item title="" id="11">
			<copy><![CDATA[]]></copy>
			<image source="JKimages/photo/jkd_hush_p11.jpg"></image>
		</item>
		<item title="" id="12">
			<copy><![CDATA[]]></copy>
			<image source="JKimages/photo/jkd_roofgod_p12.jpg"></image>
		</item>
		<item title="" id="13">
			<copy><![CDATA[]]></copy>
			<image source="JKimages/photo/jkd_meninblack_p13.jpg"></image>
		</item>
		<item title="" id="14">
			<copy><![CDATA[]]></copy>
			<image source="JKimages/photo/jkd_keralakids_p14.jpg"></image>
		</item>
	</section>
	<section title="experience">
		<item title="" id="">
			<copy><![CDATA[]]></copy>
			<image source=""></image>
		</item>
	</section>
	<section title="contact">
		<item title="" id="">
			<copy><![CDATA[]]></copy>
			<image source=""></image>
		</item>
	</section>
	<section title="seva">
		<item title="" id="">
			<copy><![CDATA[]]></copy>
			<image source=""></image>
		</item>
	</section>
</jennyKSite>